KSJAAY

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

contact@ksjaay.com KSJaay.com

SKILLS

Database management

MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Redis, MySQL, DynamoDB

Languages

JavaScript/Nodejs, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Java, Kotlin, C#

Frameworks

React, Nextjs, React Native, Express.js, Fastify, Socket.io, Discord.js, Mobx, Chart.js, Strapi.io

Tools

Github/Git, Visual Studio Code, NetBeans, pgAdmin 4, MongoDB Compass, Linux, Material UI, Styled Components, AWS Lambda, NPM

Soft Skills

Communication, Teamwork, Flexibility, Problem Solving, Time Management, Creativity

PROFILE

Recent graduate with a strong focus on both frontend and backend development, Offering 3 years of experience in software development and testing for a large user-based company. Seeking an opportunity to utilise skills in developing software for an established company.

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Nester | September 2021 - April 2022

Nester helps makes it easy for users to invest in properties. This was done by creating a simple dashboard and mobile application.

- Became the lead developer who handled any changes and issues for the frontend development and deployment within two months.
- Developing a website using Nextjs, React, and Mobx for state management.
- Using the Strapi CMS and API to develop and implement content for the website.
- Creating a custom messaging platform for mobile and PC using the telegram API.
- Developing a mobile application that allowed users to invest in properties, along with a live messaging feature.

DEVELOPER

AmariBot | August 2019 - July 2021

AmariBot focuses on developing a program that rewards users for being active within a community. Community staff members can set up custom rewards and change the difficulty of reaching rewards.

- Developing a website using JavaScript and React, used by 60,000 users monthly.
- Using discord.js/Nodejs to develop and maintain a discord bot used on over 140,000 servers and serves over 10 million users.
- Developing multiple APIs using Nodejs, TypeScript, Express.js & Fastify.
- Creating a module to cluster the application using Typescript and Nodejs. Allowing smoother/easier restarts.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, COMPUTER SCIENCE UNIVERSITY OF GREENWICH | 2018 - 2021

GRADE: FIRST

REFERENCES

Available upon request